MTV ♪
DWIGHT:
This is USP Canaan.
The federal prison
in Northern Pennsylvania.
Definitely not a great choice
for a destination wedding.
[electricity humming]
I subsisted in hellholes
like this for the last 25 years,
and to keep what's left
of my brain from deteriorating,
I read some very good literature
and wrote some very bad poems
and tried to avoid getting
shanked for a second time.
I remember when I was 17,
my father asked
what I wanted to be.
If I'd like
to be a barber like him.
I laughed in his face.
I wanted to be
a successful gangster.
In retrospect,
I ask myself
if what I chose
for an occupation
was worth 25 years
of my life.
The answer is no.
Not 25 seconds.
[buzzing]
But those are bygone times,
water under the bridge.
I married this life,
and after keeping my mouth shut
for all these years,
I'm gonna see
if it married me back.
[rock and roll playing]
- What about Scores?
- What?
There's a party, right?
Long Island.
What?
Why?
They gave me an address.
Whose house is this?
They didn't say.
[whirring]
[theme music]
[theme music ends]
Supposed to wait here.
They're ready for you.
Gang's all here.
There he is.
Nice place you got here.
How you doin', Chickie?
Uncle Dwight.
- Remember Vince?
- I do.
- Have a seat.
- At the head of the table?
That ain't the head,
that's the ass.
Witty.
Nico, Mario,
you guys gotta stand behind me?
We're watching the door,
buddy, that's all.
Well, you can watch
from anywhere
- like that corner over there.
- What can they do,
someone comes
through the doorway
the fuck over there, Dwight?
You expecting company, Glenny?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing, I just don't like
guys standing behind me.
Easy, buddy,
we're just watching the door.
Don't stand behind
my fuckin' back.
- Just give him some space.
- Where I've been,
- it's not a good idea.
- Ashpet, relax.
- Sit down...
- Not exactly
the welcome
I was expecting.
Business first.
How is business?
It's tough.
Am I supposed to be talking
to him or to you?
Chickie's my underboss now.
Vince is one of my capos.
Lot of changes.
Twenty-five years.
I was a kid
when you went away.
I got news for you,
you're still a kid,
so enjoy it.
Like I was saying,
things are tough.
Not like when you were around.
No, it was easy
when I was around.
- Just a little bit.
- Listen to my son.
Look-look-look, I don't know
what you're expecting,
okay,
now that you're back,
but we can't
just rewind the clock.
I'll tell you
what I'm expecting,
that way you'll know.
I'm expecting after doing
25 years,
to save your father's ass,
for a murder,
to save your ass,
whacking a guy,
who I actually liked,
who didn't deserve it,
I'm expecting some form
of adequate compensation.
What do you think, we're not
gonna take care of you?
Are you?
Yes.
Tulsa.
- What the fuck is Tulsa?
- It's a city in Oklahoma.
I know it's a city in Oklahoma,
I can read a map.
What the fuck are you
talking about?
I want you to go there.
Plant a flag, get it set up.
- Are you serious?
- Oh, yeah.
Dwight, I've been there,
the horse races,
Springboard Mile,
it's wide fuckin' open.
It's the future.
There's nobody doing nothing.
You can earn like crazy.
Do whatever the fuck you want.
But I'd be doing it
in Oklahoma.
There's nothing
left for you here.
I'm sorry.
But time just doesn't stop
because you fuckin' went away.
Nothing left for me here.
[sighing]
Hey.
You remember my wife Marie?
She divorced me
when I went aside,
and my daughter Tina?
I haven't talked to her
in 18 years.
She hates me.
I took an oath.
And I honored it.
I kept my mouth shut
for 25 fuckin' years.
And now all I got
to my name is a few bucks,
my suit in mothballs,
this watch,
and a fuckin' pinky ring
that you gave me.
Now, you got the balls
to tell me that,
after everything
I've been through,
after everything I've lost,
after everything
I've done for this family--
your family--
fuck-- there's
nothing left for me?!
Hey! You don't understand
how this fuckin' works.
They told you
where the fuck to go.
- That's it.
- I don't understand?
Listen, I made my bones
when you were
in fuckin' diapers.
Well, now
you're wearing diapers.
- [overlapping shouts]
- Back the fuck up!
Are you outta
your fuckin' mind?!
No, I'm not outta my mind.
- This guy has no respect.
- He's a capo, Dwight.
To you, Pete, not to me!
This wasn't our deal.
Jesus Christ, I came here
with some sense of honor.
You talk about compensation?
I'm giving you
a whole entire fuckin' city!
You're giving me
fuckin' banishment.
You kick up
five grand a week to start.
Sure, why not?
Tulsa.
Yeah, why not?
Be nice to breathe
some fresh air.
[rock and roll]
♪ Too much
of that ol' Whiskey River ♪
♪ Leaves a young man
feeling old ♪
♪ That old love
you still remember ♪
♪ Cuts you deep down
in your soul ♪
♪ Lost that girl
down in New Orleans ♪
♪ Chasing some old
voodoo dream ♪
♪ Levee broke
on Whiskey River ♪
♪ Got me tryin'
to swim upstream ♪
Oh! What was that?
It's a grasshopper.
They're harmless.
That thing's
the size of my cock.
- Excuse me?
- Actually, I'm more
endowed than that,
so-- goddamn, lady--
Relax, it's holy water,
it's holy water.
You should gargle with it
with that mouth.
These Church of God folks bless
the shit out of you,
you're not careful.
- Need a cab?
- Actually, I do.
Let me get you
right here then.
Name's Tyson,
welcome to Tulsa.
- Where to, man?
- Hotel.
Which one?
One where no one will
break my balls.
[electronic beat]
Why do they call this place
the Sooner State?
Well, you got
the football team.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's all Sooner history.
You know, when people
first came here and shit.
- Settlers.
- When was that?
Back in the day,
I guess, I don't know.
[laughing]
You're not curious?
Not really.
You know what'd be nice?
If someone
invented a device
where you could look
this shit up,
that would really be great.
You trippin', man?
The iPhone, man, you...
[laughing]
Oh, you fuckin' with me,
man, you...
[laughing]
...I can't look it up right now.
I'm-- I'm driving right now.
Yeah, all right,
forget it.
Lot of churches
around here.
It's the Bible Belt, my man.
- And you in the buckle.
- [chuckling]
So is this a wedding?
A funeral?
- Business.
- What kind of business?
The "none of
your fuckin' business"
- kind of business.
- [laughing]
I like that. Gangster
gotta be a gangster, huh?
What'd you call me?
- Say what?
- You called me a gangster.
I didn't call you no gangster,
I said a gangster gotta...
- be a gangster.
- Wouldn't that make me
a gangster?
Look, man, you obviously
ain't met no Black folks, or--
I met more Black folks
than you can count.
Well, then you would know,
you can call anybody
a gangster,
it's like saying they cool.
You think a gangster is cool?
[laughing]
Aight, it's like-- it's like
calling a dude a player.
Except I say gangster,
I ain't sayin' you in a gang.
You know, you my gangster like
a motherfucker right now--
You'd better stop
calling me that, pal.
Hey, look, ain't nobody
gonna tell me what to say
in my own cab,
you got that-- gangster?
You know what, someone's
gonna slap some good grammar
in your mouth,
and that's gonna be me--
Hey, ain't nobody gonna
talk to me like that
- in my own damn cab--
- Hey, hey!
You want some gangster?
I'll give you gangster.
Stop the car.
What is that place?
It's a dispensary.
It's where they sell marijuana.
So anybody can
just walk in there?
Yeah, it's a store, man,
what you want?
- Uh-huh, who runs it?
- Whoever owns it.
Nah, I mean,
who runs this neighborhood?
Like, what crew runs it?
Ain't no crew
up in here, man.
You're in the middle
of nowhere.
No, I got that.
Why don't you pull over there?
Well, wait a little bit
until I come out.
This will compensate you
for your time.
[doorbell jingles]
Excuse me, sir.
Let me see your medical ID.
It's okay,
I'm just looking around.
It's okay.
- I'm not gonna buy anything.
- Yeah, that's cool, man.
Thanks, appreciate it.
- Howdy.
Can I help you?
Yeah, uh,
I just got into town.
[laughing]
And I'm just looking around.
And I'm wondering,
how does all this work?
Oh, um... depends
on what you're looking for.
- Mm.
- Um, we got gummies--
- Mm-hmm.
---actual flower,
CBD oil, creams,
uh, strictly
for medicinal purposes.
If you're just looking
to get high, let me know.
- Take credit cards?
- It's cash only, sorry.
Really? Oh.
You only have one guard
and no cameras.
Where I come from,
very risky.
We don't get
much crime here.
Oh, that's good.
So, who owns this shithole?
Uh, excuse me?
I said...
who owns this shithole?
- Uh, Bodhi.
- Where's Bodhi?
In his office?
Are you asking me
or telling me?
Go get Bodhi.
I-- I can't leave
the desk, man.
Hey...
put down the pork rinds
and get Bodhi.
- What?
- You heard me, Jumbo.
Get Bodhi.
Listen, asshole,
take a hike.
Come on, man,
time to go.
[doorbell jingling]
You got a tire iron?
Yeah, yeah,
I can go to the back and--
Forget it.
- Hey, yo, that's my juice.
- Ssh.
Anybody got the time?
All right, listen,
mister, I told you to--
- Aah!
- Oh, my God!
Okay, what the fuck, Clint.
You must be Bodhi.
Yeah, who the--
who are you?
- What's your name again?
- Clint.
Clint.
Stand next to Clint.
Is this a robbery? Fuck.
Fred?
Oh, my God,
is he dead?
Nah, he's taking a break.
Excuse me, sweetheart.
Are you waiting
for an engraved invitation?
I'm way too fucking high
for this, can--
can I just wait it out
over here, please?
Put your phone on the counter
and take a seat.
I need to see your books.
My books?
Your books,
your ledgers, files,
whatever you got.
Are you...
from the government?
I just knocked
your guard out, cold,
and you think I'm a CPA?
So, you're not
with the government.
Let's take a walk.
Look at these numbers.
You're making a fortune.
[sighing, chuckling]
So, where are you
keeping this money?
It's in the bank.
I swear, it's in the bank.
Only states
legalized this stuff.
You put that money
in the bank,
and the Feds will
have it by morning.
Even you're smart enough
to know that.
I'm not lying to you.
Let me paint you a picture.
You see my shoe?
Yeah.
Now, I'm gonna take the heel
of my right shoe,
which is very sharp,
and stomp it--
[thud]
- very hard
on the top
of your left foot,
breaking at least
three or four metatarsals.
It's excruciating.
I don't wanna do it.
So, let me ask you again.
Could it be in the desk?
Could it be in the microwave?
Or could the safe be
behind that...
silly poster?
You don't need
to put yourself through this.
I wanna be your friend,
I want you to be my friend.
I don't wanna hurt your feet.
Just open
the safe, please.
My God.
How much you got there?
Half a million.
This is how it's gonna work.
I'm gonna take
20% a week.
Hey, we all got bosses,
even I answer to somebody.
But in exchange,
I'll protect you from the gangs.
What gangs?
- And the law.
- This is legal.
And if you attacked by locusts,
I'll spray 'em.
Please, don't make me have
to be an asshole about this.
Okay? I protect you.
And you pay me a commission.
[thud]
Capisce?
That's really
all you're gonna take?
What did I just say?
We're partners.
You make the money,
and I make sure you keep it.
Do we have a deal?
- Do I have a choice?
- Absolutely not.
[soft rock]
- [doorbell ringing]
- What happened to my bottle?
- I was thirsty.
- You don't want it.
It's got blood all over it.
Open the door.
When you're not driving a cab,
what kind of car do you drive?
Pssh, the repo man took it.
Here's some money.
I want you
to buy me this car.
- A Navigator?
- Yep, new one, black,
and you drive for me now.
What?
Two grand a week.
My gangster.
[laughing]
Let's go to the hotel.
Stop with that gangster shit.
[rock and roll]
Okay, Tyson,
I need you here
tomorrow morning
at 10:00 AM.
Wear a collared shirt,
10:00 AM.
[distant cars rattling]
[doorbell ringing]
Can I help you, Mister...
Manfredi.
Can you call me a cab?
Oh, we don't really get
a lot of cabs around here,
- but you can call an Uber.
- Oh, yeah, what's the number?
There's no number,
you just use the app
- on your phone.
- Oh.
Do you have an app
on your phone?
Of course.
Ms. McNamara,
call me an Uber.
[country music playing]
♪ I been workin' this job
nine to five... ♪
Minimum wage and overtime ♪
But here comes a few days ♪
Of unpaid vacation ♪
♪ And there ain't no way,
José, I'll waste 'em ♪
- Is this seat taken?
- It's all yours.
Good evening.
- How you doing?
- Good.
What'll it be?
Well, I assume
you don't have chianti.
You assume correctly.
- Okay.
- What you need's a bourbon.
Yeah, and why is that?
Well, because I was really
hoping you'd buy me one.
[chuckling]
You'll have to forgive
my friend here,
mister,
he's a goddamn mooch.
Hey, the answer is
always no until you ask.
I'll have a bourbon for me
and my two pals here.
- See?
- Bourbon it is.
Is it all right to eat here?
Best seat
in the house.
And what do you suggest?
You find better ribs
in Tulsa--
[raps counter]
- you let me know.
Ah, then ribs it is.
So, where's home, friend?
I'm gonna give you
two guesses,
but I bet
you'll get it in one.
- New York.
- You're good, very good.
I couldn't help notice,
are those
lizard boots
you're wearing?
Yes, sir, they are.
Made in Texas
just like me.
Check these out.
Made in Italy,
like my old man.
Well, how about that?
We both like dinosaurs.
There you go.
Like a beer can ♪
- Salud.
No, nothing picks me up ♪
Like a beer can ♪
I'm no expert,
but I'm pretty sure
that's not
a Lincoln Navigator.
It's my mom's.
And?
Had to go home and get it
after the car dealership.
- Where's the Navigator?
- He wouldn't sell me one.
- You show him the cash?
- What happened was
he called me a crack dealer,
threatened to call the police.
Take me there.
[music]
Good morning.
How can I help you?
[soft chatter]
No one's gonna know,
what are you worried about?
Uh-huh.
Listen, uh,
let me call you back.
Donnie Shore.
What can I do you for?
Perry Cuomo,
nice to meet you.
It seems we have
a slight misunderstanding.
See, my associate
was in earlier,
trying to buy that Navigator
that you got downstairs,
but you wouldn't
sell it to him.
Oh, boy, I am so sorry.
Why, Donnie?
Well, you know, it was
a total misunderstanding.
Like you said yourself.
The truth is,
he's a good kid.
Probably never had
a day of trouble in his life.
You see the problem is,
you see a young Black guy
with a mountain of money--
right away, you say,
hey, he's gotta be
a drug dealer.
- Oh.
- But I walk in,
in a nice suit...
and you're
not afraid anymore.
You see,
the irony is...
he's afraid
of the wrong thing.
- I'm not following.
- Well, follow this.
Aah-- I'm calling the police.
Hey, let me get
the phone for ya.
Here's the deal, Donnie.
You're gonna sell
my friend over here
the black Navigator
for $50,000 cash.
- Loaded.
- Deal?
- Okay.
This wasn't necessary.
[funk music]
This is crazy.
I forgot how good
ice cream is.
They didn't give you
ice cream in jail?
No.
Usually it was tiramisu.
That's a joke, right?
Eh...
[gasping]
Enough.
I'm gonna go wash up,
I'll meet you back at the car,
we're gonna go see Bodhi.
Hey.
How you doin', Fred?
- I've been better.
- Try the Advil.
Thanks.
What's with this puss?
That's how you
welcome customers?
Are you a customer now?
You know, you're
in the service business.
You gotta be welcoming.
- This is Tyson, by the way.
- What's up?
I got something for you.
Security camera.
And before you say
anything, yes,
I get the irony.
So, how much did
we make today?
Um, we made
a little
over five grand so far.
You're a sarcastic
little prick, aren't you?
So, tell me, where do
you get your weed from?
There's a greenhouse
and a 40-acre farm
a couple hours north of here.
That's where I buy.
They're licensed.
- Who are "they"?
- A guy named Jimmy.
Is he a front for somebody?
'Cause a lot of these farms
are fronts for cartels,
you gotta know your risks.
There was no risk
until you came along.
You know, the Feds can
waltz in here right now,
take every dollar you got,
and there's not a goddamn thing
you can do about it.
- What do you suggest I do?
- Clean it.
You mean,
uh, launder it?
I mean like
George fuckin' Jefferson.
The TV show,
before your time?
Had a lot of dry cleaners.
Not important.
What's important is
you get that money outta here
- as fast as you can.
- Okay, isn't that illegal?
You sell pot
for Christ's sake.
And... where should I put it?
Tanning salons.
Used to be big business.
Now they're big losers.
- Clubs, discos.
- A disco?
Whatever you call 'em nowadays.
I just don't wanna
get in trouble.
There's more than
one kind of trouble, Bodhi,
Especially when you have money
like that in the safe.
Now, you listen
to what I'm saying.
If you need me,
I'll be at the Western Plains.
The Western Plains?
- What?
- It's a dump.
What's the best hotel in Tulsa?
- The Mayo.
- So why am I not staying there?
You said you wanted
to be in a place
that wasn't gonna
bust your balls, right?
So I put you
in the Western Plains.
You can do your gang...
your illegal business stuff.
Go get my stuff,
I'm gonna check into the Mayo,
then I need you
to drop me off
at a place called
the Bred-2-Buck.
What in the hell is that?
Cowboy bar,
what do I know?
In the future,
if anyone asks
what I do for a living,
you tell 'em
I'm an industrialist.
What does that even mean?
My point exactly.
Nobody knows.
[music]
How you holding in, Pops?
Eh, I'm doin' all right.
My dad.
Don't trust
leaving him home alone,
so I take him to work with me
so's I can babysit.
I'm Mitch, by the way.
Dwight.
A paisan named Dwight, huh?
Dwight David Manfredi.
My parents are
proud immigrants
that named me
after the greatest general
of the 20th century.
Mm.
Let me ask you something.
How long were you in the joint?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
Twenty-five years,
last six in Canaan, you?
Little over eight, Lompoc.
Excuse me?
Are you famous?
I hope not.
Are you sure?
Oh, sweetheart,
if you have to ask
if someone's famous,
they're not famous.
Oh... can we take
a picture with you?
I don't mean this in a bad way,
but I'd rather not.
Well, you're no fun.
Tell me about it.
How long have you had
this joint?
A little over five years.
I was on the circuit.
- Bull riding.
- Bull riding, really?
Got busted up.
Addicted to pain pills.
Ran into a little trouble.
Then I started
flying around.
Well, here's to clear skies.
Hey.
Why were you rude
to my friend?
I wasn't being rude.
I just don't like
having my picture taken.
Why? Are you wanted
or something?
Nobody wants me.
You're not that bad.
That's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
Well, you messed up,
because they were gonna
invite you to the party.
- What party?
- Karaoke Castle.
Sounds exciting,
but I wouldn't really
call that a party.
What do you call a party?
Oh... ♪
[women shouting]
[all cheering]
♪ I was like, good gracious,
ass is bodacious ♪
♪ Flirtatious,
tryin' to show faces ♪
♪ Lookin' for the right time
to shoot my steam ♪
♪ You know,
lookin' for the right time ♪
♪ To flash them keys,
and I'm leavin' ♪
♪ Please believin', me
and the rest of my heathens ♪
[cheers and shouts]
♪ Penthouse, rooftop,
birds I feedin' ♪
♪ No deceivin',
nothin' up my sleeve 'n ♪
No teasin', I need you ♪
♪ To get up--
up on the dance floor ♪
♪ Give that man
what he askin' for ♪
Hey, buddy, I can't
have 'em on the stage.
- What's your name?
- Frank.
Just keep the pervs away
from the ladies, okay?
You're the boss.
I am getting so hot ♪
♪ I wanna take
my clothes off ♪
♪ It's getting' hot
in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off
all your clothes ♪
I am getting so hot ♪
♪ I wanna take
my clothes off ♪
♪ Why you at the bar, if you
ain't poppin' the bottles? ♪
♪ What good is all the fame if
you ain't... the models? ♪
♪ I see you drivin' a sportscar,
ain't hittin' the throttle ♪
♪ And I be down and do 100,
top down and goggles ♪
♪ Get off the freeway,
exit 106 and parked it ♪
♪ Ash tray, flipped it,
time to spark it ♪
Hey, buddy.
♪ Warm, sweatin',
it's hot up in this joint ♪
♪ Vocalk, tank top,
all on at this point ♪
♪ You're with a winner,
so baby, you can't lose ♪
♪ I got secrets,
can't leave Cancun ♪
♪ So, take it off
like you're home alone ♪
♪ Dance in front your mirror
while you're home alone ♪
♪ Checkin' your reflection
and tellin' your best friend ♪
Hey, Black Suit.
Come dance with me.
Tough guys don't dance.
You don't take pictures,
you don't dance.
What do you do?
Well, if I wasn't
a gentleman,
I just might tell you.
Well, if I wasn't a lady,
maybe I'd want you to.
You're something.
You live around here?
Yeah, I'm out at the Mayo.
You wanna show me
your minibar?
Haven't you had
enough already?
We'd better hurry up,
before I sober up
and lose my nerve.
You got a car?
No, not with me.
But we'll...
figure it out.
[electricity humming]
[distant train whistle blowing]
STACY:
Hey, can I wear your robe?
Yeah, go ahead.
Well.
This was very fun.
Yeah, it was great.
Just a little rusty,
you know?
It's been a while.
Really?
[sighing]
- You got a cigarette?
- Nah, I don't smoke.
I wouldn't've pegged you
as the boy scout.
Why not?
The accent, the tattoos.
Affinity for
very classy strip clubs.
I'm new in town.
Are you married?
I was, a long time ago.
- You?
- Middle of a divorce.
You were actually
the deciding factor.
How's that?
Well, I figured if I could
actually go through with it,
there was no turning back.
I'm glad to be your Rubicon.
- What's that?
- That's a river in Italy
that Julius Caesar crossed,
you know, it's--
the idiom is,
it's the point of no return.
Hm.
How old are you?
- [laughing]
- Seriously.
Why don't you just say,
hey, Dwight,
where were you
when JFK got assassinated?
All right,
where the fuck were you?
I was a senior in high school.
Seriously?
That would make you, what...
Seventy-five big ones.
Oh, my God.
Are you kidding me?
I mean... I...
I would've said
you were a hard 55.
Hard's the key word here,
isn't it?
Oh, I'm sorry,
you know what,
I'm gonna go.
Is it the age gap?
No, this is not an age gap.
This is an age canyon.
Are you hungry?
I could call room service.
No, I'm good, thank you.
I don't even know
your name.
You know, probably better
to keep it that way.
You know, normally
I would drive you home,
but I can call you an Uber,
'cause I just got an app.
I'm good--
thank you, seriously.
Um, really...
you know, I had...
I had a good time.
Maybe I'll see you around.
It was nice meeting you.
Bye.
[country music]
DWIGHT:
So, this is Tulsa.
Nice enough place,
but for me a prison, nonetheless.
That's not a complaint,
it's just a fact.
The result of a lifetime
of bad choices.
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Eddie, it's Armand.
[laughing]
The Oklahoma Kid.
Listen to me.
Is there
any fuckin' possibility
I just saw
Dwight Manfredi in Tulsa?
DWIGHT: I guess
you could say I was banished.
Exiled, sentenced to start
from scratch, and that's fine.
I'll do it.
I'll rebuild.
[sighing]
You want me to earn?
I'll earn.
I'll earn so much money
you'll choke on it.
VOICE: And in addition
to over half a million dollars
of stolen ammo,
we're also tracking
a shipment of stolen AR-15s,
which more than likely will go
to the highest bidder
among the local militia groups.
And finally...
our friends at the FBI
have alerted us
to a new visitor.
Not really our purview,
but a high-ranking mafia capo
who was recently
released from prison
has decided to grace Tulsa
with his presence.
Dwight Manfredi...
- Oh, fuck me.
- ...AKA Ike, or sometimes
Cinque Stelle, which means
"five star" in Italian.
At least two murders
to his credit,
both in the '90s,
but we are not to assume
he's some toothless tiger.
DWIGHT: Abandon me?
Ostracize me?
Alienate me
from my friends and family?
All the people I love?
I'll survive.
And here I am.
Bloodied but not beaten.
Down but not out.
And from this point on,
this city
and everything in it
belongs to me.
[theme music]
- you'd open the door.
- Seriously?
No, but it would've been nice.
I need to talk
to your supplier.
You got a last name, wasicu?
- What does that mean?
- Non-Indian person
- who steals the fat.
- That's a first.
What does your family think
about you being here?
That thing with Vince.
You gotta make this go away.
Not your mob family.
Your real family.
DWIGHT: I haven't seen
my daughter in 18 years.
There's nothing left for me
in New York.